<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<GeologicUnit>
  <row1>
    <idGeoUnit>1</idGeoUnit>
    <name>Quaternary succession</name>
    <description>The succession, lying on the post-Gelasian unconformity (QM1 unconformity in GeoMol Team, 2015 and D'Ambrogi et al., 2015), is mostly represented by clastic neritic, locally epi-bathyal, littoral, deltaic, and alluvial deposits. It is composed of sand, clayey sand, with intercalating clay, silt, polygenic pebbly and gravel levels, clay with intercalated sand, gravel, peat, and lignite beds. The age ranges from Calabrian to present.</description>
    <refGeoUnit>hlu5_Q</refGeoUnit>
    <geologicUnitType>abc</geologicUnitType>
  </row1>
  <row2>
    <idGeoUnit>2</idGeoUnit>
    <name>Pliocene succession</name>
    <description>The succession, lying on the post-Messinian unconfomity (PL unconformity in GeoMol Team, 2015 and D'Ambrogi et al., 2015), is represented by littoral-neritic to epi-bathyal deposits, locally including turbidites; it is constituted by clay, silty and sandy clay, alternating clay and quartz sand, with locally intercalated conglomerate and glauconitic sand. The age ranges from Zanclean to Gelasian.</description>
    <refGeoUnit>hlu5_PL</refGeoUnit>
    <geologicUnitType>abc</geologicUnitType>
  </row2>
  <row3>
    <idGeoUnit>3</idGeoUnit>
    <name>Mesozoic carbonate reservoir</name>
    <description>The carbonate reservoir is constituted by a Late Triassic-Middle Eocene succession bounded by the Carnian unconformity, at the base, and the top of the basinal calcareous deposits. Despite the reservoir has been considered as a whole, in some areas it is possible to distinguish a limestone-prevalent part, in the upper portion of the succession, from a dolomite-prevalent part, in the lower portion. </description>
    <refGeoUnit>hlu5_Me</refGeoUnit>
    <geologicUnitType>abc</geologicUnitType>
  </row3>
  <row4>
    <idGeoUnit>4</idGeoUnit>
    <name>Pre-rift units</name>
    <description>Permian to Carnian succession, laying on the Variscan substratum, constituted by continental to paralic siliciclastics, Ladinian volcanites, shallow water and lagoonal, locally basinal, carbonates.</description>
    <refGeoUnit>hlu5_TR</refGeoUnit>
    <geologicUnitType>abc</geologicUnitType>
  </row4>
</GeologicUnit>
